**♀** Agra (U.P.), India □ +91-7017669455

# Kush Agarwal

in kushagarwal03 bit.ly/3zCMU0K kush-03

☑ agarwalkush1999@gmail.com

Self Motivated graduand with experience in Web Development using Django framework. Diligent with learning new concepts related to my field so that I can expand my elementary knowledge to the professional skill set and formulate myself for the IT environment.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages Backend/Frontend Python, C++, SQL Diango, HTML5, CSS3

Others Database Management System, Basics Of Data Structures, Object Oriented Programming

**PROJECTS** 

**Techgram -** An Instagram clone [Link]

July — Aug 2021

- Medium for User's to Interact and share Technical Facts and Figures.
- Build Using Django Framework, Python, AWS S3 Bucket, HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript.

**Big Fuss** - News Application using Django [Link]

Mar — May 2021

- · Combined Platform for searching News from discrete sources and manual filtering of results.
- Build using News API, Django Frmaework, Python, HTML5, CSS3 and Bootstrap.

To-Do-List [Link] Sep — Dec 2020

- Based on Create-Retrieve-Update-Delete functionalities which is suitable for maintaining daily tasks.
- Build Using MVT Framework Django, HTMl5, CSS3 and Bootstrap.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Web Development Intern

June 2021 — July 2021

Remote

Technocolabs Website

- Developed a Business to Business ecommerce website in a team.
- Built and designed the efficient code as per the requirements of our client using Django, Html, CSS and JavaScript.

#### **Backend development Intern**

May 2021 — June 2021

OhLocal Website

Remote

- Worked on the Key Features and Optimization of code on company Website.
- Build and deployed the structured code as per the requirements of the team lead using Django.

### Web development Intern

Feb 2021 — March 2021

.

The Sparks Foundation Website

Remote

• Worked on a Donation Portal Site with Integration Payment feature as per client's requirements.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

SQL Basic - HackerRank [View]	July, 2021
Specialization In Python - University Of Michigan [ <u>View</u> ]	May, 2020
HTML5 and CSS3 for Web Developers - Johns Hopkins University [View]	May, 2020
Coding Ninja Hire 2.0 - Coding Ninjas [View]	Dec, 2020
Introduction To Python Programming - Microsoft Technology Associate [View]	July, 2018

#### **FDUCATION**

EDUCATION	
Bachelor Of Technology, CSE, Jaypee University Of Engineering and Technology, Guna(M.P.), CGPA: 8.6/10.0	2018 - 2022
Intermediate, AVMD Institute, Agra(U.P.), Percentage: 80.8%	May 2017
High School, St. Peter's College, Agra(U.P.), Percentage: 84%	May 2015

# **INTERESTS**

- Sketching
- · Writing

- · Playing Badminton
- Travelling